ZHIYANG WANG

CONTACT

Room 454c, 3401 Walnut St,

Department of Electrical and Systems Engineering

University of Pennsylvania,

Philadelphia, PA, 19104, USA

Mobile: (+1)2676703385

E-mail: zhiyangw@seas.upenn.edu

Homepage: http://zhiyangw.com

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research is focused on the areas of wireless communications and machine learning. I am especially interested in large-scale graph neural networks and their theoretical analyses. Some of my projects include implementing machine learning techniques to solve problems in wireless communications. I am also focused on theoretical analyses of the limits of graph neural networks as manifold neural networks and their applications on point clouds.

EDUCATION

University of Pennsylvania

2019-Present

Ph.D. candidate in Electrical Engineering

The Dean's Fellowship recipient

The Bruce Ford Memorial Fellowship recipent

Pennsylvania State University

Visiting Scholar in Electrical Engineering Advisor: Prof. Jing Yang

University of Science and Technology of China

2012-2019

Master in Electrical Engineering Bachelor in Electrical Engineering Advisor: Prof. Cong Shen Advisor: Prof. Cong Shen

Jul. 2018 - Dec. 2018

Advisor: Prof. Alejandro Ribeiro

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

University of Pennsylvania

Teaching Assistant

ESE 680-003, Graph Neural Networks

Fall 2020

ESE 224, Signal and Information Processing

Spring 2021

University of Science and Technology of China

Teaching Assistant

C programming Spring 2015

MIMO wireless communications course Fall 2017

PULICATIONS

Journal:

- Z. Wang, L. Ruiz and A. Ribeiro, "Stability to Deformations in Manifold Neural Networks", submitted.
- **Z. Wang**, M. Eisen and A. Ribeiro, "Learning Decentralized Wireless Resource Allocations with Graph Neural Networks", IEEE Transactions on Signal Processing 70 (2022): 1850-1863.
- **Z. Wang**, R. Zhou, and C. Shen, "Regional Multi-Armed Bandits with Partial Informativeness", IEEE Trans. Signal Process., Volume: 66, Issue: 21, Page(s): 5705-5717, Nov. 2018
- Z. Wang and C. Shen, "Small Cell Transmit Power Assignment Based on Correlated Bandit Learning",

Conference:

- **Z. Wang**, L. Ruiz and A. Ribeiro, "Stability of Neural Networks on Manifolds to Relative Perturbations", In ICASSP 2022-2022 IEEE International Conference on Acoustics, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP) (pp. 5473-5477). IEEE.
- **Z.** Wang, L. Ruiz, M. Eisen and A. Ribeiro, "Stable and Transferable Wireless Resource Allocation Policies via Manifold Neural Networks", In ICASSP 2022-2022 IEEE International Conference on Acoustics, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP) (pp. 8912-8916). IEEE.
- **Z.** Wang, L. Ruiz and A. Ribeiro, "Stability of Neural Networks on Riemannian Manifolds", , In 2021 29th European Signal Processing Conference (EUSIPCO) (pp. 1845-1849). IEEE. **Best Student Paper Award**
- **Z. Wang**, M. Eisen and A. Ribeiro, "Unsupervised Learning for Asynchronous Resource Allocation in Ad-hoc Wireless Networks", In ICASSP 2021-2021 IEEE International Conference on Acoustics, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP), pp. 8143-8147. IEEE, 2021.
- L. Ruiz, **Z. Wang** and A. Ribeiro, "Graph and Graphon Neural Network Stability", In ICASSP 2021-2021 IEEE International Conference on Acoustics, Speech and Signal Processing (ICASSP), IEEE, 2021.
- **Z. Wang**, M. Eisen and A. Ribeiro, "Decentralized Wireless Resource Allocation with Graph Neural Networks", In 2020 54th Asilomar Conference on Signals, Systems, and Computers, pp. 299-303. IEEE, 2020.
- C. Shen, **Z. Wang**, S. S Villar and M. van der Schaar, "Learning for Dose Allocation in Adaptive Clinical Trials with Safety Constraints", In International Conference on Machine Learning, pp. 8730-8740. PMLR, 2020.
- **Z. Wang**, Z. Ying, and C. Shen, "Opportunistic Spectrum Access via Good Arm Identification", IEEE GlobalSIP 2018, Anaheim, California, USA, Nov. 2018.
- **Z. Wang** and C. Shen, "Small Cell Power Assignment with Unimodal Continuum-armed Bandits", 2018 IEEE International Conference on Communications Workshops on 5G-UDN.
- **Z. Wang**, R. Zhou, and C. Shen, "Regional Multi-Armed Bandits", Proceedings of the Twenty-First International Conference on Artificial Intelligence and Statistics (AISTATS), PMLR 84:510-518, Playa Blanca, Lanzarote, Canary Islands, April 9-11, 2018.
- **Z. Wang**, C. Shen, X. Luo, M. van der Schaar, "Learn to Adapt: Self-Optimizing Small Cell Transmit Power with Correlated Bandit Learning", IEEE International Conference on Communications (ICC), 2017.

SKILLS

Programming: Pytorch, C, JAVA, MATLAB, Origin

Documentation: MS Office, LaTex

AWARDS AND RECOGNITIONS

EUSIPCO Best Student Paper Award

Sep. 2021

Awarded by EURASIP to 3 student finalists at the paper competition Q&A

The Bruce Ford Memorial Fellowship

2019

Excellence fellowship granted by the University of Pennsylvania in addition to The Dean's Fellowship

National Award for Graduates

Sep. 2017

Granted by China's Ministry of Education to graduate students with excellent academic performance.

IEEE ICC student Travel Grant

2017

Awarded by IEEE to cover for travel expenses.

The First Prize in Graduate Academic Scholarship: USTC	2016-2019
Excellent Award: The Undergraduate Research Program in USTC	Oct.2015
First prize of Contemporary Undergraduate Mathematical Contest in Model Division	ing, Anhui Sep. 2015
Outstanding Student Scholarship: USTC	2013-2015
Outstanding Volunteer of the Chinese Young Volunteers Association	2013